Viewers, whatever medium you are using to view us here,
you are declared healed, in the name of Jesus!
That your bone - be free from sickness!
That your blood - be free from sickness!
Your organs - be free from sickness, infirmity!
His healing hand is on you!
Jesus' healing hand is on you!
Be healed!
Be delivered!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Whatever hinders your deliverance, healing, blessing -
be it unforgiveness, anger, jealousy, envy - give way, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to give way, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips and begin...
Unforgiveness, unbelief, doubt - give way, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to give way!
Give way!
In the name of Jesus, receive your healing!
Receive your freedom!
Receive your deliverance!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Rejoice!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
TT: Mel Flowers 19/07/2018
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 26/07/2018